insidetrade.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | InsideTrade.com

_Inside Washington Publishers_ provides you with exclusive, top-quality news on issues affecting federal policies in all areas of interest, including the environment, defense, trade, energy and healthcare. You may obtain this timely and valuable information through a wide variety of daily, weekly, biweekly and monthly services, which include investigative news reports, comprehensive news summaries and issue analyses. In an effort to facilitate use of this wealth of information, you may access _Inside Washington Publishers’_ content via the Internet. In addition, you may take advantage of a variety of electronic services provided by _Inside Washington Publishers_. _Inside Washington Publishers_ provides this Internet Privacy Policy to confirm its dedication to your privacy and to encourage broad use of its electronic services.

## Information Collected by _Inside Washington Publishers_

When you browse _Inside Washington Publishers_ web sites, the web servers automatically collect some information about your visit, including your IP address, type of browser software and operating system, the date and time of your visit, the pages visited and the Internet domain from which you accessed _Inside Washington Publishers’_ web site. This information may be used to verify that only authorized users are accessing our sites, and that this access conforms to underlying subscriber agreements; this information will not be sold or rented to outside parties, unless required by law. Except for the site-monitoring information described above, _Inside Washington Publishers_ does not collect any personal information unless it is voluntarily provided by you after you complete a request for a subscription or service or send an e-mail to _Inside Washington Publishers._ You will know when you are providing this information because you will be required to complete and submit a form. This form will include information like your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. Some subscriptions or services may involve payment by credit card, and any credit card information provided to _Inside Washington Publishers_ is used only to bill for the requested subscription or service, and is not stored or used by _Inside Washington Publishers_ for any other purpose.

If you would like to see data collected about you, or request that your data be erased, please contact us at [privacy@iwpnews.com](mailto:privacy@iwpnews.com) \-- we will respond within 30 days. 

## Use of Information Collected by _Inside Washington Publishers_

_Inside Washington Publishers_ is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of our subscribers. Subscriber information collected is used by _Inside Washington Publishers_ to enhance its services and to provide you with additional services. For example, _Inside Washington Publishers_ may use the collected information to determine your interests and to provide you with topical information or notices. If you would rather not receive any such information or promotional materials from _Inside Washington Publishers_ , please send an e-mail message stating your wish to not receive such information to [info@iwpnews.com](mailto:info@iwpnews.com).

_Inside Washington Publishers_ does not disclose any information collected from you to any third-party, unless required by law.

## Security Safeguards and Technological Advances

_Inside Washington Publishers_ seeks to maintain the security of all information collected through its web site by protecting against unauthorized access to, and disclosure of, such information. _Inside Washington Publishers_ also seeks to further advance its services by providing additional electronic services as they become available. These changes may cause _Inside Washington Publishers_ to revise its data protection practices and its Internet Privacy Policy. Any changes to the Internet Privacy Policy will be made available at this site.

## Additional Services

For additional information about _Inside Washington Publishers’_ Internet Privacy Policy or to change any information provided to _Inside Washington Publishers_ through this site, please contact us, via e-mail at [info@iwpnews.com](mailto:info@iwpnews.com).
